Guide to the Silicon Valley Ephemera Collection, 1976- M0443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Silicon Valley ephemera collection
1976-2008
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
M0443
28 Linear Feet
A collection of ephemeral publications issued by or referring to the microelectronics industry of California's "Silicon Valley." Includes promotional material, price lists, conference proceedings, newsletters, etc.
Scope and Contents
An artificial collection of ephemeral publications issued by or referring to the microelectronics industry of California's "Silicon Valley." Includes promotional material, price lists, conference proceedings, newsletters, etc.
Acquisition Information
An artificial collection kept by the library; multiple donors.
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use. The Media materials require at least two weeks advance notice to use in order to allow staff time to have use copies made from the original items.
Santa Clara County (Calif.) -- Industries.; Microelectronics industry -- California -- Santa Clara County.; Computer engineering.
- Publications, Series 1
  - General, Subseries 1.1
    - 1-800-Batteries. Product catalog, 1996; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition note
      Transfer, 1998.
      Scope and Contents note
      Product catalog for 1-800-Batteries, Fall 1996.
      Power Express.
    - 3Com Corporation. Papers, 1986-1988; 6 items. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      3Com Corporation
    - Abhiweb Corporation. Promotional pamphlets, 1997; 2 items. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Acer Technologies Corporation. Promotional flyer, 1987; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Action Audio Electronics. Price list, 1977; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Action Audio Electronics
    - Active Imaging, Inc. Promotional materials, 1996; 2 items. (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Transfer, 1998
    - Activision catalog, 1985; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Adobe Systems. Adobe PageMaker classroom in a book, Macintosh, Ver. 6, 1995; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Transferred, 1998
    - Adobe Systems. Promotional flyers, product catalogs, typeface libraries, and "Communication Handouts," [1 of 2], 1991-1995; 15 items (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Adobe Systems. Promotional flyers, product catalogs, 1998 - 1999; 9 items (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Adobe Systems. Promotional flyers, product catalogs, typeface libraries, and "Communication Handouts," [2 of 2], 1991-1995; 15 items (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Adobe Systems. SourceBook, vol. 1, 1988; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Adra Systems, Inc. Pamphlet, 1995; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Pamphlet entitled CONCURRENT ENGINEERING PARADIGMS: MATRIX, LOTUS NOTES AND GROUPWARE.
    - Advanced Micro Devices. The Am2900 family data book, 1976; 1 v. (172 p.) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. Promotional brochure and news release, 1997-2001; 2 items. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Transfer, 1998 and 2001.
    - Advanced Semiconductor Equipment Exposition. Announcement, 1987; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Advanced Semiconductor Equipment Exposition
    - Advanced Technology Center, Santa Clara Valley, California. Promotional article, circa 1980; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Photocopy of article that traces the history of Silicon Valley. At head of article is a note that "this is one of a series of special reports on centers of high technology throughout the United States by Peter J. Brennan in association with Development Counsellors International, Ltd."
      Brennan, Peter J; Development Counsellors International, Ltd.
    - Advantage Production Technology, Inc. Product information pamphlet, circa 1990; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - AI list, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - AimNet. Promotional brochure, 1996; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - ALPS America. Promotional flyer, 1987; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Aldus Corporation. Product catalog, 1993; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Altra. Advertising flyer, circa 1996; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Advertising flyer for "Felix" mouse.
    - Amazon.com. Appledesign printout, 1999 Apr 12 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Apple Computer, Inc. Dynamic Graphics, Inc. Megahaus Corporation. Quar
    - Amazon.com. Speeding the Net: the Inside story of Netscape and how it challenged Microsoft: printout, 1999 Mar 3 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - American Association for Artificial Intelligence. AI Magazine, Vol. 11, no. 5,., 1991 Jan; 1 v. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - American Association for Artificial Intelligence. AI Magazine, Vol. 13, no. 3, 1992 Fall; 1 v. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - American Association for Artificial Intelligence. AI Magazine, Vol. 14, no. 1-2, 1993 Spring - Summer; 2 v. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - American Association for Artificial Intelligence. AI Magazine, Vol. 16, no. 1-2, 1995 Spring - Summer; 2 v. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - American Association for Artificial Intelligence. Conference registration packet, 1989; 2 items. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - American Association for Artificial Intelligence. Miscellaneous items, 1990-1995; 25 items (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Includes fellows list and nomination forms, symposia bulletins, calls for papers, membership material and registration brochures for AAAI-93 and IAAI-93 in Washington, DC, and IJCAI-95 in Montreal, Canada.
    - American Multisystems. Info gold: brochure, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Ampex Corporation. Annual reports, 1954-1957; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ampex Corporation. Annual reports, 1958 - 1961; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ampex Corporation. Memoranda, 1959 - 1960; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Includes two company memos on corporate identity, 1959 & 1960.
    - Ampro Computers, Incorporated. Price list, 1986; 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Ampro Computers, Incorporated
    - Andromeda Software, Inc. Product catalog, 1993; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Applied Biosystems, Inc. Promotional material giving extensive product information, 1986-1988; 7 items (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Applied i. Promotional flyer, 1986; 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Applied i.
    - Appoint Inc. Promotional brochures, circa 1991; 6 items (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Promotional brochures for MousePen, Thumbelina, Gulliver and Computer Crayon.
      International Machine Control Systems, Inc.
    - Aquas, Inc. Promotional brochures, 1996; 2 items. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - ArborText Inc. Promotional pamphlet and guide to Standard Generalize Markup Language (SGML), 1992-1993; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - ARESCOM Inc. Promotional brochures, 1996; 4 items. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Artec Electronics, Inc. Papers, undated; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Artec Electronics, Inc.
    - Artificial Intelligence Publications. The Artificial Intelligence report: proofs and publications, Vol. 1, nos. 1-7, 1983 Aug-1984 Jul; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Corrected proofs and final copies of the AI Report.
      Artificial Intelligence Publications;; Allen, John; Llull, Harry; Robinson, Lou
    - Artificial Intelligence Publications. The Artificial Intelligence report: proofs and publications, Vol. 1, nos. 8-12, 1984 Aug-1984 Dec; 5 items (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Artificial Intelligence Publications. The Artificial Intelligence report: proofs and publications, Vol. 2, nos. 1-3, 1985 Jan-1985 Mar; 7 items (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Artificial Intelligence Publications. The Artificial Intelligence report: proofs and publications, Vol. 2, nos. 4-10, 1985 Apr-1985 Oct; 9 items (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Artificial Intelligence Research Group. Brochure, 1985; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Allen, John; Artificial Intelligence Publications
    - Ascend Communications, Inc. Promotional pamphlets, 1996; 4 items. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Ascent, Inc. Product announcements, 1986; 3 items. (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Ascent, Inc.
    - AstroSearch., 3 v. (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Journal entitled AstroSearch, v. 1, n. 1, March-April 1983, v. 1, n. 2, May-June 1983, v. 1, n. 5, November-December 1983.
    - Atari. The Catalog, Autumn, 1986; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Atari, Inc.
    - Atron. Bugbusters: user's manual, undated; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Atron.
    - Autodesk, Inc. Product catalog, conference catalog, and flyers for Discreet (Div. of Autodesk, Inc.), 1995-2001; 8 items. (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Transfer, 1998-2001.
      Discreet.
    - Avantos Performance Systems, Inc. Product brochure, 1993; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 8)
      ManagePro 2.0 for Windows product description.
    - Award Plus. Product catalog, 1996; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Barnes-Hind. Product information and ephemera, 1966, undated; 3 items (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 1, nos. 1-9A, 1983 Aug-1984 Jan (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 2, nos. 1 - 6, 1984 Jan-1984 Jun (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 2, nos. 7 - 11, 1984 Jul-1984 Dec (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 3, nos. 1 - 9, 1985 Jan-1985 Oct (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 3, nos. 10 - 11, 1985 Nov-1985 Dec (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 4, nos. 1 - 6, 1986 Jan-1986 Jun (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 4, nos. 7 - 11, 1986 Jul-1986 Dec (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association newsletter, Vol. 5, nos. 1 - 8/9, 1987 Jan-Aug-Sep (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Microsoft Corporation. Promotional flyers, circa 1987-2000; 3 items. (Box 4)
      Microsoft.
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association. BAMDUA BAKUP news, Vol. 1, nos. 1 - 4, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bay Area Micro Decision Users Association flyer (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Bering Industries Inc. Product announcement, 1986; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Bering Industries Inc.
    - Biowire.com mailer, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bit Basement. Price list, undated; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 6)
      The Bit Basement.
    - BIT Software Inc. Promotional flyers, 1983-1986; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 7)
      BIT Software Inc.
    - Borland International. Promotional pamphlets, 1987-1993; 7 items (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Promotional pamphlets detailing Borland products and services
    - Borland International. Promotional pamphlets, 1990; 8 items (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Borland International. Turbo Pascal reference manual, ver. 2.0, 1983; 1 v. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Borland International. Turbo Technix: the Borland language journal, Vol. 1, no. 2, 1988 Jan-Feb; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Borland International. Turbo Technix: the Borland language journal, Vol. 1, no. 3, 1988 Mar-Apr; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Borland International. Turbo Technix: the Borland language journal, Vol. 1, no. 4, 1988 May/June; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Borland International. Turbo toolbox, 1984; 1 v. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Brøderbund Software, Inc. Brochures, undated; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Brown Bag Software. PC-Outline reference manual, 1986; 1 v. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Brown Bag Software. Productivity software review, 1988 - 1989; 2 issues (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Byte Shop. Papers, undated; 3 items (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Byte Shop.
    - Cadis. Promotional pamphlet, circa 1996; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Promotional pamphlet for Krakatoa web-publishing software.
    - California Business Machines. Price list, undated; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 20)
      California Business Machines
    - California Commission on Industrial Innovation. Winning Technologies: A New Industrial Strategy for California and the Nation, 1982; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Executive summary of the Report of the California Commission on Industrail Innovation. For release: September 2, 1982.
    - California Extreme 2K!, 2000; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Capella Worldwide Networking, Inc. Promotional material, 1995-1997; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Promotional material for Capella Worldwide Networking, Inc.
    - CBooks Express. Promotional materials and schedule of author appearances, circa 1990; 3 items (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Children's software, catalogs, pamphlets and magazines, [1 of 3], 1991-1997; 23 items (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Children's software, catalogs, pamphlets and magazines, [2 of 3], 1991-1997; 23 items (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Children's software, catalogs, pamphlets and magazines, [3 of 3], 1991-1997; 23 items (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Churchill Club. The Orator, 1998 Mar; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - ClariNet Communications Corporation. Promotional materials, 1997; 4 items. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      2 promotional cards for ClariAlert, a brochure for ClariNews and a listing of news categories.
    - Claris Corporation. Promotional pamphlets, 1992-1993; 5 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Promotional pamphlets.
    - Cognos Associates. Reports [1 of 2], 1983-1986; 4 items (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Gift of Judith K. Larsen, 1986.
      Includes: PROFESSIONAL AND TECHNICAL WOMEN IN ELECTRONICS, CHANGING LIFESTYLES IN SILICON VALLEY, U.S. POLICY AND THE SEMICONDUCTOR INDUSTRY: AN INDUSTRY PERSPECTIVE, and HIGH-TECH LAY OFFS: SILICON VALLEY AND SILICON GLEN. Authors include Judith K. Larsen, Linda Kimball, Carol Gill, and Carolyn Mattison.
    - Cognos Associates. Reports [2 of 2], 1983-1986; 4 items (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Comdex conference and expo, 1999; 3 items (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Companies with over 500 employees, 1986 Nov; 1 item (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Compute!'s Gazette, Issues no. 4-5, 9-21, 1983 - 1985; 15 items. (Box 6)
    - Computer Currents buyer's guide, 1986 Summer - Autumn; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Dessauer, John H.; Xerox Corporation.
    - Computer Faire. Papers, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Proceedings and programs for the West Coast Computer Faires
      Warren, Jim C., Jr.; Computer Faire RAG (Random Access Guide) Silicon Valley Gazette.
    - Computer Faire. Papers, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Computer Faire. Papers, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Computer Faire. Papers, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Computer Faire RAG (Random Access Guide) Silicon Valley Gazette.; Warren, Jim C., Jr.
    - Computer Faire. Papers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Computer Faire. Papers, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Computer Faire. Bay Area Computer article re:, 1984 Mar 13 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Computer Headware. Book announcement, undated; 1 item (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Computer Headware.
    - Computer help, Vol. 1.01 - 1.05, 1989 Sep-1990 Jan (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Computer Museum of America promotional flyer, 1982; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility. Promotional flyer, circa 1986-1987; 4 leaves. (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility
    - Computer Shack. Papers, undated; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Computer Shack.; Dean, Gilbert.
    - Computer Swap, Inc. Papers, 1986-1987; 3 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Computer Swap, Inc.
    - Concentric Network Corporation. Promotional brochure, 1997; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Concurrent Controls, Inc. Promotional pamphlets for Applica U2 user sharing system, 1996; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Conductus, Inc. Promotional pamphlet, 1994; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Transfer, 1988
      Promotional pamphlet detailing company operations.
    - Control Data Corporation. Promotional postcard, 1995; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Convenience Living Systems. Promotional flyer, undated; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Convenience Living Systems
    - Conway Publications, Inc. Industrial Development, 1963; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Two copies of Industrial Development, August 1963. Reference study entitled Sites For Science
    - Corvus Systems, Inc. Promotional flyer, 1986; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Corvus Systems, Inc.
    - CP/M, 1982 - 1983; 2 item. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - CPSR (Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility). Brochure, undated; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Creative Networks, Inc. Company literature, 1996; 9 items. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Cyber FreeWay. Promotional flyer, circa 1996; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - CyberCheer. Promotional card, circa 1995; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - CyberEdge. Journal issue and conference program, 1993-1994; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 14)
      CYBEREDGE JOURNAL, March/April 1993 and VIRTUAL REALITY EXPO '94 CONFERENCE & EXHIBITION conference program
    - CyberMedia Group. Promotional materials, 1994-1995; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Transfer, 1988.
    - CyberMind. Promotional flyer, circa 1995; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Promotional flyer advertising various 3-D games.
    - Dell. Promotional mailer, circa 1995; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Promotional mailing advertising new computers.
    - Delrina Technology, Inc. Product catalog, 1995; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - DeltaPoint, Inc. Promotional brochures for web development software, 1996; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Demo 96 conference materials, 1996; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Desktop Publishing. Desktop Publishing, Jan 1987; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 21)
      Desktop Publishing
    - Digiscents promotional flyers, 2001; 4 items (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Digital Graphics Interactive. Promotional pamphlet, circa 1990; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Digital Group. Papers, undated; 2 items (Box 8, Folder 24)
      The Digital Group.
    - Digital Hollywood, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Digital Systems Research Center. The 1995 SQL reunion: people, projects, and politics / ed. by Paul McJones. -- (SRC Technical note, no. 1997-018), 1997 Aug 20 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Directory of Internet Professional Services, Vol. 1, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Dr. Dobb's Journal of Software Tools. Promotional flyers, circa 1987; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Dvorak's Software Review. The software boutique, issue #1, undated; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Dvorak, John C.; Dvorak's Software Review
    - DYMAX. Booklist, undated; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 30)
      DYMAX.
    - Early, James M. Title: Limitations and alternatives in future silicon LSI technology, 1978; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Eastman Kodak Company. Promotional flyer, 1993; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Promotional flyer.
    - Echelon, Inc. Product announcement, 1986; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Echelon, Inc.
    - Electric Power Research Institute (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Electronic Arts. Product catalog, 1994; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Electronic Marketing Analyst. -- Harrison-Hoge Industries, Inc., 1994; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 36)
      Electronic Systems.
    - Electronic Systems. Catalog, 1977; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - EMPaC International Corporation. Promotional brochures, circa 1996; 2 items (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ESL Inc. Job announcement, undated; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      ESL Inc.
    - Everex. Product announcement, Nov-86; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Everex
    - Evers, Bill (Congressman). A Place to Live: A Position Paper on the Housing Crisis, the Jobs/Housing Imbalance, and the Decay of the Urban/Suburban Environment, 1980; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Item stamped Bill Evers, Congress, in upper right corner.
      Evers, Bill
    - Exodus. Promotional flyers for Internet access, circa 1995; 2 items. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Expoconsul International, Inc. Expo West 86, 1986; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Expoconsul International, Inc.
    - Fabrik Communicactions, Inc. Promotional brochures, e-mail and netiquette guides, 1996; 5 items. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Faggin, Federico. Microprocessors in perspective: typescript, together with newsrelease and article about Faggin by Elvia Faggin, 1988-1989; 3 items (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Gift of Elvia Faggin, 1988, and Enzo Coniglio, Instituto Italiano di Cultura, 1989
      Microelectronics industry -- California -- Santa Clara County.
    - Ferris Research. Promotional materials, circa 1995; 6 items. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - First Floor, Inc. Promotional pamphlets, 1997; 3 items. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Fog International Computer Users Group. Magazines, 1990-1991; 5 items (Box 9, Folder 13)
      FOGHORN & FOGLIGHT magazines, May/June/July 1990 and August/September/October 1990; FOGHORN, #s 247, 248 [1991]. Notes: The previous publication FOGHORN resumes with #245, with this combination of titles.
    - Foothill Research Center. Grand opening invitation, 1990 June 21; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Fortune Systems Corporation. Promotional flyer, 1982; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Fortune Systems Corporation
    - Four11 Corporation. Promotional pamphlet for RocketMail, circa 1995; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Free Market. Flyer, circa 1981; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Gift of Daniel W. Collison, 1986
      Free Market
    - Fujitsu Software Corporation. Promotional brochure, 1995; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Game Writing Group. Flyer, circa 1981; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Gift of Daniel W. Collison, 1986.
      Game Writing Group
    - Gates, Bill. Clarinews@clarinet.com posting re: founding of ICOS Corp., 1990 July 3; 1 item. Note: item missing (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Gen2 Ventures. The Gen2 Report, circa 1986-1987; 3 pp. (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Gen2 Ventures.
    - General conference on nanotechnology: conference materials, 1992; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - General Magic, Inc. Promotional brochure for Magic Cap software, 1996; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Grafpoint. Promotional flyer, circa 1987; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Graphics Gathering. Microsm: newsletter, 1981-1982; 3 items (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Graphics Gathering
    - Greater Bay Area Library Council. Informational pamphlet, circa 1996; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 26)
      LIBRARIES & THE INTERNET pamphlet.
    - Greater Silicon Valley Implant Users Group. Flyer, 1986; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Greater Silicon Valley Implant Users Group
    - Greenblatt, Julius, publisher.Western States Electronics Directory, 1962; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Greenblatt, Julius, publisher.
    - H-Square Engraving Systems. Product brochure, 1985; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 29)
      HiTech International, Inc.
    - Hercules Computer Technology. Product information, 1987; 3 items (Box 9, Folder 30)
      Hercules Computer Technology
    - High Tech Gays. Brochure, circa 1986-1987; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 31)
      High Tech Gays.
    - HiTech International, Inc. Price list, circa 1986-1987; 3 items. (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Homebrew Computer Club. Papers [1 of 2], 1976-1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      Newsletters and announcements.
      Homebrew Computer Club
    - Homebrew Computer Club. Papers [2 of 2], 1976-1987 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - i-Planet, Inc. Promotional brochure, 1996; 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Icon Review [1 of 2], 8 items. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Issues of ICON REVIEW: THE RESOURCE FOR OUTSTANDING MACINTOSH SOFTWARE, Summer 1985, Fall 1985, Summer 1986, Winter 1986, Spring 1987, Summer 1987, Fall 1987, Summer 1988, vol. 11.
    - Icon Review [2 of 2], 8 items. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - IMSAI Manufacturing Corporation. Papers, 1977-1986; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
      IMSAI Manufacturing Corporation.
    - Industrial Affiliates Symposium. Communication in science: challenges for the nineties: to honor James Murray Luck, 1989 Oct 20-21; 1 item (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - InfoWorld. Newsletter, 1981; 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Info World
    - Innovative Applications of Artificial Intelligence conference materials, 1990; 1 item (Box 10, Folder 7)
      International Business Machines Corporation.